const OOPS = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept?",
        options:[ "Encapsulation", "Polymorphism", "Exception", "Abstraction"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which feature of OOPS described the reusability of code?",
        options:[ "Abstraction", "Encapsulation", "Polymorphism", "Inheritance"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which feature of OOPS derives the class from another class?",
        options:[ "Inheritance", "Data Hiding", "Encapsulation", "Polymorphism"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which operator from the following can be used to illustrate the feature of polymorphism?",
        options:[ "Overloading <<", "Overloading &&", "Overloading ||", "Overloading +="],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following definition is incorrect for polymorphism?",
        options:[ "Polymorphism helps in redefining the same functionality", "Polymorphism concept is the feature of object-oriented programming (OOP)", "It always increases the overhead of function definition", "Ease in the readability of the program"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which function best describe the concept of polymorphism in programming languages?",
        options:[ "Class member function", "Virtual function", "Inline function", "Undefined function"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following feature is also known as run-time binding or late binding?",
        options:[ "Dynamic typing", "Dynamic loading", "Dynamic binding", "Data hiding"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which among the following is not a member of the class?",
        options:[ "Virtual function", "Const function", "Static function", "Friend function"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following class is known as the generic class?",
        options:[ "Final class", "Template class", "Abstract class", "Efficient code"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following OOP concept binds the code and data together and keeps them secure from the outside world?",
        options:[ "Polymorphism", "Inheritance", "Abstraction", "Encapsulation"],
        answer: 4
    }
];

export default OOPS;